OK, now we're going to start the Wi-Fi application so we can test it.
So first, let's go down to the Wi-Fi upstart function.
And copy it and then go to Maine, see?
And first, let's clean this up and make a comment.
Application entry point.
And now let's include envious flash storage.
And we also want to include.
Our Wi-Fi app that each.
And now let's clear out the EP, men.
And say Initialise NCVHS.
And here we're going to initialize non-volatile storage in the recommended manner because it actually
attempts to handle errors by raising the flash and retrying instead of simply aborting as the Espérer
check would do.
So here, let's say ESP error type.
Return equals India's flesh in it.
And then say, if return.
Is ESB ever envious?
No free pages.
Or the return?
Is ESP error?
Envious.
New version found.
Then will espera check.
Envy as fleshy race.
And then they'll set the return.
To the result of invest flesh in it.
Then let's ESB air check.
The final return result.
And we're only checking for these specific errors, as not all errors can be resolved by flashing and
retrying.
All right.
So if we follow the no free page's error.
This happens when the politician doesn't contain any empty pages, and here it's recommended to erase
the whole partition and call in flesh in it again.
And the new version found.
This happens when the envious partition contains data in a new format that's not recognized by this
version of code.
All right, so now let's start with five.
By calling wi fi upstart.
And then now let's build.
And flesh when you're ready.
And now let's keep our event handler messages handy here while we open a terminal.
So let's come here and open the terminal.
And here the terminal shows a couple of messages from the event handler and also a cue messages here.
So there's our AP start.
And our start http server Q message as well.
All right.
Great.
So now let's try to connect.
So just go to your available Wi-Fi networks and find your SPF 30 to.
And then type your password.
I just left minus password, so I'll connect.
And now we can see that the event handler captured the event for AP.
Stay Connected event.
Which is the event right here?
And also, we can see that our DHP server setup has assigned an IP to our station in the same network.
All right, great.
So that's it for now, and we'll continue to expand Wi-Fi throughout the course and in the next section,
we'll talk about the FTP server.